POPOOLA EMMANUEL

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



+(234) 905 355 2140

olaayo10@gmail.com



Lagos, Nigeria



emmapopo.com



Making user interfaces more beautiful. One pixel at a time.

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

JAVASCRIPT

UX DESIGN

RAPID PROTOTYPING

USABILITY TESTING

JQUERY

PHP & MYSQL

C# .NET

PROFILE

Award winning front-end developer with more than 8+ years experience building pixel perfect websites and UIs.

Flexible in working environments having positioned for startups, digital agencies, and fortune many companies. Focused on helping agile teams with UI development for large scale web or mobile apps.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FAVCODE54

MAR 2018 - PRESENT

- * Website Development
- * UX Design
- * Mobile Applications Development

NCK TECHNOLOGIES

OCT 2017 - PRESENT

- * Full-stack Web Development
- * Team Lead

SELF EMPLOYED

OCT 2010 - SEPT 2017

- * Full-stack Web Development
- * Mobile App Development
- * Windows Apps Development

EDUCATION

YABA COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

2014 - 2017

National Diploma - Computer Science School of Technology, Yaba, Lagos

NIIT 2014 - 2016

Masters in Software Engineering Ikeja Centre, Lagos.

YABA COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY SECONDARY SCHOOL

2008 - 2014

TECHNICAL SKILLS



Javascript







PHP



MYSQL



(C

JQuery



UI/UX

HTML 5



React

TOOLS









Adobe XD Git Sublime Text Android Studio